Marist Record and the Circle
Marist College
The Record and the Circle: The Student Newspaper of Marist College
Marist Archives and Special Collections 3399 North Road, Poughkeepsie, NY 12601
3.1.1.1.1
Items in this collection do not circulate and may be used in-house only.
scope
- The Record and the Circle: The Student Newspaper of Marist College
  - 1961 Reynard's Record
    - Photographs, 2.1
      - Glass Plate Negatives, 2.1.1
        - Frank R. Roberson, 2.1.1.1
          - Austria, 2.1.1.1.1
              - Vol. 1 Num. 1 February 14, 1961, 1 (Box 1173)
              - Vol. 1 Num. 2 February 21, 1961, 2
              - Vol. 1 Num. 3 February 28, 1961, 3
              - Vol. 1 Num. 4 March 7, 1961, 4
              - Vol. 1 Num. 5 March 14, 1961, 5